

CONTACT



+49 173 8054417



jelavicnikola@gmail.com



nikolajelavic.github.io/portfolio



github.com/NikolaJelavic



10369 Berlin

SKILLS

- Attention to details
- Verbal & Written Communication
- Analytical skills
- Thinking out of the box

LANGUAGE

- Serbo-Croatian Native
- English C1
- German B2

HOBBIES

- Social activism
- Traveling
- Cooking

NIKOLA JELAVIC

QUALITY ASSURANCE

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Manuel Tester with 2 years experience in Quality Assurance.

During NGO activism, I have improved my organizational skills, attention to details, and verbal communication.

I have recently finished Web Dev bootcamp and I am searching for a job where I can improve my skills in automating tests.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Movinga GmbH (Berlin) - Quality assurance (full-time)

January 2016 - October 2016

- Jira (Kan Ban and Scrum)
- Collaborated in writing Test Plans and Test Cases
- Involved in the complete SDLC
- Selenium IDE, PyCharm and Ghost Inspector for automation
- Tested mobile application and game
- Postman app for checking emails
- Backend testing using SQL
- Basic things in Salesforce
- SQL injections

Flexperto GmbH (Berlin) - Quality assurance (full-time)

January 2015 - January 2016

- Redmine
- Testing audio/video(WebRTC) communication, scheduling in Calendar, rating system, messaging and chat system, payments, interactive whiteboard, file transfer, digital signature
- System tests, Acceptance tests and Monkey tests
- Selenium IDE and Ghost Inspector as plugins for automation
- SQL injections

EDUCATION

Fullstack Bootcamp 05/2023-08/2023

Spiced Academy, Berlin 12 weeks full time program

Informational technologies 2008-2011

Bachelor's Degree

SOCIAL ACTIVISM

2013-2015:NGO League of Social Equality (Novi Sad) - President 2010-2012:NGO-League of Social Equality (Novi Sad) - Vice President